[Music]
[音乐]
one of my favorite features in Inkscape
Inkscape中我最喜欢的功能之一
is having the ability to create a
是有能力创建一个
document and save it as a template that
记录并另存为模板，该模板
you can launch directly from within
您可以从内部直接启动
Inkscape anytime you want this is useful
Inkscape随时随地使用此功能非常有用
because it means you won't have to waste
因为这意味着你不需要浪费时间
time formatting your document every time
每次格式化文档的时间
you go to create certain types of
您可以创建某些类型的
designs that you may regularly work with
您可能会经常使用的设计
like YouTube thumbnails channel art
喜欢YouTube缩略图频道艺术
business cards invoices and so on if you
名片、发票等，如果你
go to file new from template you'll see
从模板转到文件新建，您将看到
a list of templates that are already
已存在的模板列表
formatted for whatever it is you'd like
为您想要的任何格式设置格式
to create and if you're using Inkscape
要创建Inkscape，并且使用Inkscape
version 1.0 or later you can add your
版本1.0或更高版本，您可以添加您的
templates to this library by going to
模板复制到此库，方法是转到
file save template and from there you
文件保存模板，并从那里开始
can choose a name along with some other
可以选择一个名称和其他一些名称
metadata and whatever it is you're
元数据，不管它是什么，你
currently working on an Inkscape will be
目前正在开发的Inkscape将是
saved to that library as a template that
作为模板保存到该库中，
you could launch anytime you'd like all
你可以随时发射你想要的一切
you have to do is go to file new from
你要做的就是从
template and there it will be because of
模板，并且它将在那里，因为
this I've been able to generate a list
这是我已经能够生成的一个列表
of eleven templates for common design
共有11个模板，用于通用设计
items like print-ready business cards
可打印的名片等物品
and trifold brochures with bleed lines
还有一式三份的宣传册，上面有出血线
and dpi already accounted for and in
和dpi已经占到并在
this video I'll be sharing them with you
这个视频我会和你们分享
and just to be clear these are not
我要澄清的是，这些并不是
designs these are just blank templates
设计这些只是空白模板
that you can load into your template
您可以将其加载到模板中
library and use to create your own
库，并使用它创建您自己的
designs in the description of the video
视频描述中的设计
I'll have a link to where you can
我会有链接到你能找到的地方
download a zip folder with these
使用以下内容下载一个压缩文件夹
templates in them once you open the
当您打开
folder you'll see a list of templates
文件夹中，您将看到模板列表
including brochures business cards
包括宣传册和名片
contact icons for business cards
名片的联系人图标
Facebook banners Google Ads and so on
Facebook横幅、谷歌广告等
like I mentioned earlier all you have to
就像我前面提到的，你所要做的
do is open one of these files with
DO是用以下命令打开其中一个文件
Inkscape then go to file save template
Inkscape然后转到文件保存模板
and if you're using an earlier version
如果您使用的是较早的版本
of Inkscape that doesn't yet have the
Inkscape还没有
same template feature you can simply
相同的模板功能，您只需
navigate to see Program Files
导航以查看程序文件
Inkscape share templates and copy and
Inkscape共享模板并复制和
paste all of the files into that folder
将所有文件粘贴到该文件夹中
and the next time you launch Inkscape
下一次启动Inkscape时
you will be able to create a new
您将能够创建一个新的
document based on one of those templates
基于其中一个模板的文档
this method also works for Inkscape
此方法也适用于Inkscape
version 1.0 if you don't feel like
1.0版，如果您不想
opening each document one by one and
逐个打开每个文档并
saving it although the pathway is
拯救它，尽管路径是
slightly different for this one navigate
这一次导航略有不同
to see Program Files share Inkscape
查看程序文件共享Inkscape
place I'll have this information posted
我会把这些信息张贴在网上
in the description as well one thing I'd
在描述中还有一件事我想
like to point out is that some of these
我想指出的是，其中一些
templates may be a little confusing when
在以下情况下，模板可能会有点令人费解
you first open them take the brochure
你先打开它们，拿着宣传册
template for example it has separate
例如，它有独立的模板
layers with boundaries that represent
具有边界的图层表示
the bleed cutoff line another example
出血截止线又是一个例子
would be the business card templates as
将名片模板作为
you may already know business card sizes
你可能已经知道名片的大小了
differ by countries so I created a
不同的国家，所以我创建了一个
master file with every size included if
包含所有大小的主文件，如果
you're unsure of how this works then I
你不确定这是怎么回事，那么我
would recommend checking out the PDF
我建议您查看PDF
document in the zip folder it has links
其包含链接的压缩文件夹中的文档
to some articles that I've written in
我写的一些文章
the past where I explained how some of
在过去，我解释了一些
these templates work in more detail
这些模板的工作原理更为详细
other templates like the switch banner
其他模板，如交换机横幅
for example are more self-explanatory
例如，更不言而喻
because it's just a document set to a
因为它只是一个设置为
specific width and height the templates
模板的具体宽度和高度
are free to download and use however
但是可以免费下载和使用
you'd like without any need for
你会喜欢而不需要任何
attribution I'm releasing them into the
归属我将把它们发布到
public domain so use them however you
公共领域，所以无论您如何使用它们
want you can even redistribute them if
希望您甚至可以在以下情况下重新分发它们
you'd like
你会想要
finally if you want to learn more about
最后，如果您想了解更多关于
how Inkscape perks be sure to check out
Inkscape的额外福利一定要查清楚
my Inkscape course it's a collection of
我的Inkscape课程它是一个集合
over 60 videos where I go over every
超过60个视频，我每看一遍
single tool and feature in Inkscape and
Inkscape和中的单一工具和功能
I explain what it is and demonstrate how
我解释它是什么并演示如何
it works I'll have a link in the
它有效我会在
description if you want to check that
如果您想检查，请进行描述
out if you have any questions leave a
如果您有任何问题请留言
comment below and as always thanks for
下面评论，一如既往地感谢
watching
看
you
你